{
    "subject": "resource/Philip_Rivers",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Alabama",
    "human_readable": "Philip Rivers was born in Alabama.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8500456213951111,
            "question": "Where was Philip Rivers born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6671539545059204,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Philip Rivers was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5578904151916504,
            "question": "Philip Rivers' birthplace is in which region of the US?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.391189843416214,
            "question": "Are there any other famous athletes from Alabama besides Philip Rivers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32985720038414,
            "question": "Is Philip Rivers originally from the Southern United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16527771949768066,
            "question": "Philip Rivers might have been influenced by the strong sporting tradition of which state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10510386526584625,
            "question": "What state is known for producing football players like Philip Rivers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08859848976135254,
            "question": "Alabama is associated with which popular American sport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06979931890964508,
            "question": "What is known about Alabama's culture and sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03946150466799736,
            "question": "Can you name a famous NFL player from Alabama?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Philip Rivers was born in Alabama.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3984_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Alabama's culture and sports?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3984_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alabama is associated with which popular American sport?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3984_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is known for producing football players like Philip Rivers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3984_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3984_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Philip Rivers was born in Decatur, Alabama. This is mentioned in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3984/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3984/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances where it is stated that Philip Rivers was born in Decatur, Alabama. Therefore, the statement \"Philip Rivers was born in Alabama\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}